I have family out there my brother lives
to our south my dad's to our south and
San Diego my mom just moved out there so
that's nice
my brothers settled down he got married
that was cool it was a great wedding
went down there for the wedding that was
real nice I've been to some crazy
weddings I had a friend got married she
married a professional hockey player
they spent so much money on this wedding
they gave us live butterflies and
cardboard boxes that we held on to
during the ceremony when the couple came
out of the church were supposed to let
the butterflies go because it's supposed
to be all like you know like whoo stupid
is what it was the Catholic service is a
long service was hot couple came out of
the church were like hey congratulations
release the butterflies uh hey get up
[Music]
you're on like I think you guys heard
the butterflies hope you're happy in
your brand-new lives
murderers they were smart and they
thought about they would have given us
caterpillars and by the time the
ceremony was over
fresh new butterflies I had a friend in
my 20s it got married he got cold feet
he tried to run out of the back door of
the church was a little crazy was like a
movie we stopped him he's fine he's
happily married now we saw it coming
though because he he felt like he kind
of got coerced into getting married was
like an erosion of his willpower over
time like a slow wearing down over the
years liquor like a grinding away like
that old Tootsie Pop commercial like how
many licks does it take to get to the
center of my delicious Tootsie Pop so I
don't know maybe we should move in
together a Wan hey let's watch Dancing
with the Stars a tomb
I think he's spent too much time with
your friends a three I'm pregnant
three legs mr. al been some great
weddings my my cousin got married on the
beach in Florida the hell is nice fun
this is like ten years ago was one of
the best weddings everyone to its very
lavish shirt right there steps you were
in our meal chicken well this is a
little Karlin table says tonight's on
tray free-range chicken ten years ago I
didn't know what that was
that's the waitress it's like what does
that mean free-range chicken she's
really into she's like IO AC Mo's
chicken they grow up squished up in a
cage the whole life
this chicken grew up free on the range
so everyone enjoy
I was like all right let me see if I can
taste the difference here to me you know
you're right this chicken tastes like it
used to be happy and what's the
difference this will taste depressed I'm
sending it back I don't need a chicken I
can't eat just a chicken if you're like
a vegan or something you know I'm just
joking
don't get upset some people take that
very seriously just a joke I understand
the logic behind the free-range chickens
I've seen the documentaries just kidding
around
I say that because I did that joke I was
in Hartford Connecticut and I did that
joke and after the show because of that
joke this vegan guy wanted to beat me up
yeah but because he's a vegan he
couldn't
[Applause]
[Music]
you lack the essential vitamins and
proteins necessary
to throw a decent punch plus you see it
coming because the skins translucent
just watch the muscles contracting
uppercut blood you Telegraph that but
again
celery stick go get it subscribe to
drive our comedy for even more of the
world's largest collection of clean
comedy